{"question": "What is the Platinum Label marathon and why is it the first of six annual marathons in 2023?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is foreign coverage?", "answer": "Foreign"}
{"question": "Who was the Overseas Filipino Worker (OFW) who was found dead in Kuwait in January 2023?", "answer": "Jullebee"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the upcoming 63rd Ptuj carnival?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the suspect's name and where did they lose their R$20,000?", "answer": "Ezequias"}
{"question": "What is the name of the ceremony that recognized the best recordings, compositions, and artists?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who won the 2022–23 Coupe de France?", "answer": "Nantes"}
{"question": "Who is the petitioner in the Devu G. vs State Of Kerala & Ors. case, and what was the issue they raised?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the Salvadoran gang crackdown referred to in El Salvador as the Régimen de Excepción (Spanish for State of Exception) and the Guerra Contra las Pandillas (Spanish for War Against the Gangs)?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the shortage of sugar in the domestic market?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "Who is the Academy of Television Arts & Sciences, and what is the Academy of Television Arts & Sciences responsible for?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the Redding brothers' band, and when was Otis Redding III born?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who were the two gunmen?", "answer": "They"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the XXVII Island Games (also known as the 2027 NatWest Island Games for sponsorship reasons) and when will it be held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How many clashes occurred in April 2023 between Palestinians and Israeli police at the Al-Aqsa Mosque?", "answer": "3"}
{"question": "Who were the Sikhs who protested against the manhunt of Amritpal Singh in March 2023?", "answer": "Pro-Khalistan"}
{"question": "What was the final league table after the Premier League had finished, and how many points did Liverpool finish on?", "answer": "Liverpool"}
{"question": "Who won Best International Act: EME at the 2023 Brit Awards?", "answer": "Ariana"}
{"question": "What was the purpose of the Stardom New Blood 7 event?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the current lineup of Dark Angel?", "answer": "Gene"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the SGDC-2 satellite?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What are the dates and locations of the 2023 IBA World Boxing Championships?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who was the last King of the Hellenes?", "answer": "Constantine"}
{"question": "What was the theme of the 7th Crunchyroll Anime Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of Operation Wuambushu in Mayotte?", "answer": "To"}
{"question": "What is the planned Indian constellation of Inter-satellite communications satellites, and what is the name of the first satellite?", "answer": "Indian"}
{"question": "What is the 15th Negeri Sembilan state election and when will it be held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the Eurovision Choir 2023 and when will it take place?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Where is the tournament being held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What will be the exact ONE WORD answer for the question?", "answer": "Seville"}
{"question": "What is the significance of the armed raid on the Jenin refugee camp?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the cause of the Pakistan economic crisis?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "When is the La Vuelta Femenina taking place?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the band's name before being signed to a major label?", "answer": "Sumika"}
{"question": "Who is Xi Jinping and what is his role as general secretary of the Chinese Communist Party and Chinese president?", "answer": "Xi"}
{"question": "What is the name of the 2023 Pan American Games?", "answer": "Santiago"}
{"question": "What is local news?", "answer": "Local"}
{"question": "What is the date for the 2022 All Africa Music Awards (AFRIMA)?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What applications are emphasized in the International Year of Basic Sciences for Sustainable Development?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the Triangle Derby I event?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the position of Governor (Başkan) and when will the election be held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the prize?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What were the civil unrest incidents that started in France on 19 January 2023, and who were the opponents of the pension reform bill?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "Which film won the award for Best Original Screenplay?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who was the outgoing party leader of the Swedish Centre Party and who nominated Muharrem Demirok to succeed him at the party's party leadership election?", "answer": "Muharrem"}
{"question": "What is the name of the host for the 20th Anniversary IFTA Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the date and location of the sinking of migrants?", "answer": "On"}
{"question": "What is the name of the 2023 Metro FM Music Awards and when will it premiere live on SABC1?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How many members are elected in the National Assembly in the upcoming general election?", "answer": "Seven"}
{"question": "What is the name of the Man of the World 2023 pageant and the date it will take place?", "answer": "Man"}
{"question": "What is the name of the South African city where the Miss Grand South Africa pageant will be held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Why did the protests occur?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who won the Best Actor award at the 16th Asian Film Awards?", "answer": "Bai"}
{"question": "What were the circumstances leading to the massacre?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who is the Russian military blogger who died in the Saint Petersburg bombing?", "answer": "Maxim"}
{"question": "Which award was presented by Martin Scorsese at the 75th Directors Guild of America Awards?", "answer": "Best"}
{"question": "What is the 2023 United Nations Climate Change Conference or Conference of the Parties of the UNFCCC, and what is its purpose?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the Chinese space station that Shenzhou 16 will be launched to?", "answer": "Tiangong"}
{"question": "What is the United Nations High Seas Treaty?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the date and location of the 58th Academy of Country Music Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who won the 2023 Princess Auto Players' Championship?", "answer": "Canadian"}
{"question": "What is the first time that Tanzania has reported a Marburg virus disease outbreak?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "What is the name of the professional wrestling tournament that took place on March 19, 2023 at Lucha Libre AAA Worldwide?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which measures aimed to increase the Census' effectiveness in response?", "answer": "One"}
{"question": "What is the location of the Second European Political Community Summit?", "answer": "Mimi"}
{"question": "What is the date and location of the 50th ceremony of the Annie Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the Nairobi Declaration and why is it being made by South Sudanese military officials?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which party is contesting the by-election?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who qualified for the 2023 Belgian Cup Final?", "answer": "KV"}
{"question": "What was the 2022–23 North American winter like?", "answer": "An"}
{"question": "Who were the recipients of the Platino Awards, and what were their categories?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the fourth tropical storm and fifth tropical cyclone of the 2022–23 South-West Indian Ocean cyclone season, and how did it impact Madagascar?", "answer": "Cheneso"}
{"question": "What is the company's ownership structure?", "answer": "Wallenius"}
{"question": "What is the title of \"Stay\" performed by Monika Linkytė in the Eurovision Song Contest 2023, and who is the host of the Eurovision Song Contest 2023?", "answer": "Stay"}
{"question": "How often are drones being reported to the authorities?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was Geneina like before the British arrived?", "answer": "Geneina"}
{"question": "What is the online newsroom on the website of a corporation?", "answer": "An"}
{"question": "What is the name of the ongoing three-day professional wrestling pay-per-view event promoted by Mexican wrestling promotion Lucha Libre AAA Worldwide?", "answer": "Triplemanía"}
{"question": "What was the purpose of the indirect presidential election in Vietnam?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What day will municipal elections be held in Israel in 2023?", "answer": "It"}
{"question": "When is the Toronto mayoral by-election and what is the role of the candidate?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which British television shows received nominations for the 2023 British Academy Television Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the focus of entertainment journalism?", "answer": "Entertainment"}
{"question": "Which venue will be the location for the Miss Grand Japan 2023 pageant?", "answer": "Tokyo"}
{"question": "How has the Nigerian Naira been affected by protests against the 2023 Nigerian presidential election?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What were the similarities between the events of the Brazilian Congress attack and the January 6 United States Capitol attack?", "answer": "Many"}
{"question": "How did the Russian authorities say that Ukrainian armed group crossed the border and attacked the villages of Lyubechane and Sushany?", "answer": "An"}
{"question": "What was the main event of the All Star Junior Festival 2023?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the 2022–23 season like for Galatasaray?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the film nominated for Best Picture at the 38th Film Independent Spirit Awards, and who won the award?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who will be the next President of China?", "answer": "Xi"}
{"question": "What is the coalition formed by Gerindra Party and National Awakening Party, and what is the party's policy in the 2024 presidential election?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Where is the 2023 Vilnius summit being held?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the International Space Station?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "In which categories are the awards given?", "answer": "In"}
{"question": "Who is the reigning Miss Universe 2022?", "answer": "Miss"}
{"question": "What is the format of the playoffs in the 2023 NBA season?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How long is the Golden Jubilee of Carl XVI Gustaf?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the home where the improvised explosive device exploded in Weare, New Hampshire on April 26, 2023?", "answer": "NH"}
{"question": "What alleged attacks have occurred between Congolese and Rwandan forces in 2022, according to the passage?", "answer": "Congolese"}
